{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806374008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806374008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806379890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806379889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806388291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806388291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806397936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806397936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806409733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806409733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806416069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806416069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806422277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806422277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806427965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806427965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806434558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806434558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806440955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806440955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806448203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806448203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806510189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806510189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806516030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806516030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806522420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806522419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806528407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806528407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" c872cec3-f81a-4d70-b41a-c9178e947abf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806537556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806537555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806537791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806537791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806538765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806538764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806540053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806540053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806543041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806543040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806543893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806543892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806544214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806544214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806545462","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806545461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806549025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806549025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806550021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806550021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806550289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806550288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806551256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806551255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806554152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806554151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806555200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806555200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806555680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806555679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806560233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806560231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806560379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806560379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 99b96a79-2056-4eab-95ec-f64309bfe6e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806578039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806578039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dudu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806580272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806580272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dudu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806584659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806584659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806585959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806585959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806591696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806591696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806592710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806592710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806595756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806595755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kinu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806596720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806596720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kinu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nu"," userResponse":" nu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806599620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806599619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806600208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806600207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806606021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806606021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806614031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806614031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806620291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806620291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806621853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806621853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806625984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806625984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806627122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806627122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806629996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806629995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806631052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806631052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806635242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806635242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806636327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806636327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_simba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806639254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806639253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" swa"," userResponse":" swa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806640987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806640987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806647229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806647229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" ya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806648143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806648142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806650012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806650012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" cb1c9478-39cb-454d-8707-e0209c81d557"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806663559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806663558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806664816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806664816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806667013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806667012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kundi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806667883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806667883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kundi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806670724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806670724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_punda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806671474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806671474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_punda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806677271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806677271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_punda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806678280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806678280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_punda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806681180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806681180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806682281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806682281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806685900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806685900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806686843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806686843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806690038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806690038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwe"," userResponse":" mwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806691071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806691071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806694031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806694031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_raha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806694918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806694918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_raha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806698270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806698270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806704520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806704520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" ya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806705487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806705487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806708660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806708660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806709522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806709521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806714515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806714514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806715714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806715714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806718291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806718290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" f8ff2bd5-5140-4841-bfc4-5673a7ffa73d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806732027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806732027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806733034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806733034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806736207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806736207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806741978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806741978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806743039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806743038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806746134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806746134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806747074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806747074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806750052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806750052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goli"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806751084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806751084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_goli"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806754464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806754464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806760593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806760593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806761790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806761790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806766469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806766469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806772590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806772590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806773847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806773847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806778270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806778270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806784091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806784090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806785160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806785159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806788488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806788488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pini"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806794634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806794634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pini"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806798003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806798003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pini"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806801648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806801648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jembe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" je"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806802389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806802389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jembe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806805119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806805119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_duma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806805784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806805784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_duma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806807868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806807867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" ce83c249-2e07-4f9f-8feb-a07936c6791b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_duma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806818002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806818002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" e0f9ffaa-ff77-47a1-8e28-b8590ae6e1af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806823842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806823842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" e0f9ffaa-ff77-47a1-8e28-b8590ae6e1af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806836152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806836152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806841749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806841749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806849336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806849336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_choo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806855209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806855209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_choo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806858246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806858246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_choo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806876056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806876056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806882204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806882204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806882787","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806882786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806907732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806907732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pera"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806909440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806909440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pera"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806916298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806916298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_boga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806917196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806917196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_boga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806920927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806920927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twi"," userResponse":" twi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806921694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806921694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806925739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806925739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ju"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806931742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806931742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ju"," userResponse":" ju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806932709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806932708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806935883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806935883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngo"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806941662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806941662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ngo"," userResponse":" ngo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806942731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806942730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806945374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806945374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dada"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806946322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806946322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dada"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806949094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806949094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lori"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lo"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806949725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806949725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lori"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" lo"," userResponse":" lo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806950897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806950897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lori"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806952490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806952489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 14b62581-8f3f-4a71-b0c2-5895bd7cf8ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_lori"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806989379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806989379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806995330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806995330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549806996675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549806996675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807002114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807002114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807002719","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807002719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807006903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807006903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" be"," userResponse":" be"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807008158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807008158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807013693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807013692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807020352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807020352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807022063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807022062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807023302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807023302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6a05a3b0-ab26-4b68-85ad-3df4184b2336"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807032371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807032371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807032593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807032593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807033557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807033557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807034830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807034829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807037676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807037676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807038520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807038519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807038833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807038833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807040067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807040067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807040109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807040109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807040179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807040179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_164538"," gameId":" 6301d8a8-56c8-441e-9a23-b86e2de161f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}